sharemods.com 2019-07-12

# ShareMods.com - Upload & Share Mods

## Privacy Policy

Sharemods.com (we or us) is a provider of online file storage service. Your use of the Sharemods.com site is governed by this Privacy Policy.   
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to respect the privacy of the visitors on its website, included as: to inform you about the service we provide, about the ways how the personal information you submit to us may be used, and how this information is protected on our website. We may update this policy from time to time, so we ask you to check the policy regularly. 

Managing Your Information Preferences  
You can check, review, correct, update, remove or change your Personal Information by changing the relevant setting in your Sharemods.com profile or account (if you have one), or by e-mailing us at [contact us form](http://sharemods.com/contact.html) . Please note that it is your responsibility to keep the password confidential, therefore do not share it with anyone. You are entirely responsible for keeping your password inviolable. 

**Information We Collect and How We Collect It**

Personal Information.   
You can use certain features of the Service without providing us with any information that identifies or may be used to directly identify you ("Personal Information"). We collect Personal Information only if you choose to share it with us when you register with Sharemods.com, including your username, e-mail address. The decision to provide this information is optional. Sharemods.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with non-affiliated companies. 

Usage Data.  
We automatically collect usage information that does not directly identify an individual user ("Usage Data"), such as: the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the links you use, and the time and duration of your use of the Service... Usage Data to help us understand how people use the Service, and to enhance the services we offer. For example, we use IP addresses are logged and used to identify our visitors as well as manage download limitations and user sessions. 

**Cookies**

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small files containing a chain of characters, stored by your browser on your device (computer, mobile, tablet etc.).   
Cookies cannot be used to identify who you are, without other information. However, they record information relating to your browsing of the Website, such as your preferences for example, which may be read directly by our servers when you subsequently visit or send requests to the Website. 

**How are cookies used?**

Most cookies that may be stored or read when you browse the Website are used solely to enhance your browsing experience on the Website and make certain services on the Website available. If you decide not to allow those cookies, this could adversely affect your experience on the Website and could even block your access to certain services offered on the Website. We disclaim all liability in that respect.   
Cookies that are necessary for the provision of the service you have requested may also be installed. They can be used, for example, to remember your interface customisation choices while you continue browsing the Website or to maintain your session open during your time spent browsing the Website, after you have logged in and until you log out.   
Some cookies are used for statistical purposes and for web analytics, to help us improve our services and our Website. Those cookies are anonymous.   
Third parties may also install and use cookies on the Website. Those cookies are governed by the cookie policies implemented by those third parties and we recommend that you read them. We do not have any control over the cookies installed by third parties. 

**How can I manage cookies on my device and/or disable cookies?**   
Cookies can only be installed on your device with your consent, unless they are strictly necessary for the provision of a service you have requested or they are solely designed to enable or facilitate electronic communications. Your prior consent is not required for anonymous cookies used solely to obtain statistics and for web analytics. However, you may disable the installation of those types of cookies on your device.   
When you visit the Website, a cookie banner informs you that we use cookies. You accept cookies if you continue browsing our Website by visiting another page of the Website or clicking on a link in the Website. 

Your consent is valid for 13 months and corresponds to the maximum retention period for our cookies. After 13 months, you will be asked to consent to cookies again.   
You may also manage your cookie preferences at any time, to enable or disable them, by following the instructions stated below. 

**You can manage the installation of cookies on your device in the Internet settings menu of your browser. However, if you decide not to allow certain cookies, this could adversely affect or even block your access to certain services offered on the Website. You may disable the installation of cookies on your terminal through your browser settings using the following procedures:**

Firefox 

Click the Menu button and choose Preferences   
Select the Privacy & Security panel and go to the History section.   
In the drop-down menu next to Firefox will, choose Use custom settings for history.   
Uncheck Accept cookies from websites. 

Google Chrome 

Click More, and then Settings and then Advanced.   
Under Privacy and security click Content settings and then Cookies.   
Turn Allow sites to save and read cookie data off. 

Microsoft Internet Explorer 

Select the Tools button and then select Internet Options.   
Select the Privacy tab and under Settings, select Advanced. Choose if you want to allow, block or be prompted for first and third-party cookies. 

Safari 

Click Preferences and then Privacy.   
Select an option relating to cookies and website data. 

Opera 

Click Preferences and then Advanced.   
Select an option relating to Cookies. 

iOS 

Click Preferences and then Safari.   
In Privacy, select Block all cookies. 

Android 

Click More, and then Settings and then Site settings.   
In Cookies, turn Cookies off. 

Windows Phone 

Click Settings and then Advanced.   
In the Cookies from websites drop-down menu, select Block all. 

**You can also regularly clear the cookies installed on your device.**

**How We Use Information and When We May Share Information**

Generally.

We generally use Personal Information only for purposes of providing and communicating with you about the Service, including responding to your requests, making payments, notifying you of new products or services, and otherwise communicating with you about the Service. We will not disclose Personal Information to third parties without your consent, except as explained in this Privacy Policy. 

Ad Networks.  
We may work with third-party advertising and marketing companies ("Ad Networks"). These companies may collect and use information about your use of the Service in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Advertisements may be shown via the Services, or third-party websites. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons to collect information about your use of the Service, of other Internet services and websites. 

Google Analytics.  
We also uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies," which are text files placed on your computer, to help Sharemods.com analyze how users use our Service. We use this information to help us understand how people use the Service, and to enhance the services we offer. 

Data Retention.  
We will hold your Personal Information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity. If you cancel your registration and your account is deleted Sharemods.com will no longer use the Personal Information, and personal information will be deleted immediately. 

Credit card security.  
All purchases on Sharemods.com are handled by third party card processing company. Sharemods.com does not arrange and/or save numbers or any information from your credit cards. 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement.  
Sharemods.com cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate for any of the following reasons: to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas); to protect the safety, property, or rights of Sharemods.com, any our members, or any third party; to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity; or to comply with the law. 

Be Careful When You Share Information  
Please be aware that whenever you share information in an uploaded file via the Service, that information may be accessed by the recipient. That means that anyone with access to the shared file can potentially use it for any purpose, including potentially uploading, storing, or sharing files, sending unsolicited communications, or redirecting payments. We reserve a right to review your account content for violations of our Terms and Conditions. If we determine that your files violate the Terms and Conditions, we may ban your account and will attempt to contact you. We reserve the right to cancel your account and remove the files from our servers. 

**Security**

How we protect your information.  
Sharemods.com is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. We employ reasonable physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Service, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you upload, store, share, transmit, or provide on or through the Service, and you do so at your own risk. 

Manage Content and Links to Other Websites  
You have the right to access, upload and download your files and access and correct your personal information at any time. You may also grant access to your account files to other users through sharing linklists or file download links. We do not own your account content, and will access your files for troubleshooting only. All uploaded files in Sharemods.com is public available and averyone can download them. Also, all uploaded files is visible in search engines. 

Our Service may also contain links to other websites, or allow others to send you such links. The use of the Service to provide a link to material on Sharemods.com servers or to a third party's website does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over the content uploaded and shared using the Service. We also do not exercise control over third-party websites. You access such content or third-party websites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before providing any information to the operator of the website. 

Children's Privacy  
We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. By using our Services, you promise that you are at least 13 years old. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13, we will terminate any account that user may have with Sharemods.com. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.
